So here's another way to deal with non-linear data like this.
那么这里有解决非线性数据的另一种方法
What we do is we use a piecewise linear function,
我们需要使用分段线性函数
which is really just a combination of lines that will fit the data well.
相当于几条直线连接起来 较好地拟合数据
And how do we do this? Well, we can use our good old friends, the neural networks.
那么我们如何做到呢？ 它对我们来说已经不陌生了 神经网络
So, here's are an example of a neural network used for
这里是一个用于分类的神经网络例子
classification with n inputs and some bias units,
包含 n 个输入和一些偏置单元
and a bunch of ReLu activation functions.
和一批 ReLu 激活函数
And at the end, you can see a sigmoid function,
最后你可以看到一个 Sigmod 函数
and this is because we're using the neural network for classification, so,
这是因为我们使用神经网络进行分类
we want the final answer to be a number from 0-1.
所以我们得到的最终答案是 0 到 1 之间的数字
But what if we don't need this neural network for
但是如果我们使用神经网络
classification instead we need it for regression?
并不是为了分类 而是为了回归 应该怎么办呢？
So we don't want it to return a number from 0-1.
我们不想得到 0 到 1 之间的数字
Instead, we want it to return any number.
而是希望得到任何数字
Well, let me show you a very simple trick.
让我给你展示一个非常简单的技巧
All you have to do is to actually remove the final sigmoid unit,
实际上你只需要删除最后一个 sigmoid 单元
and just return the value you had before.
就可以返回你之前得到的值
This value is the weighted sum of the outputs of the previous layer, and that's it.
这个值是前面各层的输出加权总和 就是这样
And in order to train this network,
为了训练这个网络
we would use a different error or loss function.
我们可以使用不同的误差或损失函数
It would just be as we've seen in the section given by the mean squared
这就成为我们看到的这部分 给定均方误差函数
error function or the square of the difference between the label and the prediction,
或标签与预测之间的方差
that is (y - y-hat) squared.
即 (y-y-hat)²
Of course, we'd be adding it or averaging over all the points.
当然 我们也可以增加这个 或对所有点求平均值
But mainly, if we use this function and combine with the back propagation,
但是大体来说 如果我们使用这个函数 结合反向传播
we'll be able to train our neural network just as we did for classification.
我们能够像分类一样训练我们的神经网络
So, this is how I picture regression of networks in my head.
这就是我绘制的脑海中神经网络回归
On the hidden layer, we'll have a bunch of linear functions and the inputs,
在隐藏层 我们有一些线性函数和输入
which are X and the biased unit 1,
分别是 X 和偏置单元 1
and there's linear functions are simply lines.
这些线性函数只是直线
Then we combine them with the ReLu one.
然后我们将它们与 ReLu 结合起来
And the way to combine them with the ReLu is by turning the part of
把它们与 ReLu 结合起来 是通过
the line that is negative or underneath the X axis into zero.
把直线的负值或位于 X 轴下方的部分转变为 0
Now, the next layer just takes
现在下一层只是求出
linear combinations of these linear functions combined with ReLus.
这些线性函数与 ReLu 结合后的线性组合
This is how these linear combinations look,
这就是线性组合的样子
they look like piecewise linear functions.
看起来像是分段线性函数
We can also use other activation functions here such as sigmoid or TanH.
我们在这里也可以使用 sigmoid 或 TanH 等其他激活函数
We would still train these networks using
我们依然使用反向传播训练这些函数
back propagation to minimize the mean square error.
最小化均方误差
And these networks would look like this when you're combining
这些网络看起来会是这样
linear functions with sigmoids and then taking linear combinations of those.
当你把线性函数和 sigmoid 结合起来 得到线性组合
So, in general, this is fantastic news.
所以总体来说 这是个振奋人心的消息
This means that we can use neural networks not just for classification,
这就意味着我们可以使用神经网络 并不是为了分类
but also for regression,
而是为了回归
just by removing the final activation function
只需要删除最后一个激活函数即可